别害怕  亨利少爷
Fear not, young master Henry.
你会勇敢的
You will be brave.
因为你本就勇敢
Because you are brave.
我们面临严峻的机遇和挑战
We face dire challenge and chance.
我们的性命
Our lives...
生活方式
our way of life...
危在旦夕
it hangs in the balance,
犹如一块易碎的玻璃立在电线上
a fragile glass standing on a wire,
位于柏油马路上方
high above the asphalt,
而我们祈祷着阴天不会落雨一滴
as we pray for not one drop of rain under an overcast sky.
但我依然在笑
And yet, I smile.
我们会战斗  我们会流血
We will fight, and we will bleed...
但我依然在笑
and yet I smile.
我们要面对敌人
We shall face men,
一些因形势所迫而助纣为虐
some cornered into their roles by circumstance,
另一些是嗜血成性的亡命凶徒
some desperate murderers thrilled by blood.
我们要终结他们
We shall end them all.
亦如终结今日的进攻
As is our charge this day.
亦如终结我们的痛苦
As is our sorrow.
但我依然在笑
And yet, I smile.
我们将离开至亲
We will leave our loved ones...
穿过危险重重的道路
to traverse a dangerous road.
远离和平  踏入战场
Rushing out of peace into war.
但我依然在笑
And yet, I smile.
因为我们会从今日的战斗中找到荣耀
For we will mine glory from the rock of struggle this day.
我们将会尊重和保护这座死人之地中的
We will honor and protect this -- this bastion of life
活人堡垒  我们必将胜利
in a land of the dead, and we will win.
你们要信任国王  我们必将胜利
You trust the king -- we will win.
今天我微笑
I smile...
大笑
I laugh...
我万分欣喜
I rejoice this day...
因为在今天
for on this day,
我们梦想相通
we are joined in purpose and vision
我们心神合一
we are of a singular heart and mind.
今天  我们团结一致
On this day, we are one!
是的
Yeah! ?
-对  -没错
- Yes. - Yeah!
团结一致
We are one!
对
Yeah!
团结一致
We are one!
对
Yeah!
团结一致
We are one!
《行尸走肉》
陛下
Your Majesty!
数量太多了
There are too many!
快走
Just go!
你能走路吗  陛下
Can you walk, Your Majesty?
必须用手杖撑着
With my cane. I have to.
我扶你
I got you.
你不能为我冒险
You cannot endanger yourself for me.
陛下  我必须这样做
Your Majesty... I have to.
蠢货  拿上枪
Asshats, get those guns,
我们赶紧走
and let's screw the hell off now!
我们需要帮助
We need some help here!
你们需要的是他妈加速
What you need is to hurry your asses up!
你们要是不在我走过转角之前
If you're not out of here with those guns
把枪搬出来
by the time I round this corner,
我就揍扁你们
I am gonna flay your asses!
说到做到
It is real now!
我们快好了  老天啊
We're almost done! Jesus!
-没搞错吧  -怎么
- What the hell? - ?What?
只剩这几箱0.50子弹了吗
Those are the only .50-cal buckets we got?
剩下的在库里
Got the rest in the pool.
这些只是用来打他们的
This was just to tear 'em up.
我们至少还有...
We got at least --
让她走
Let her go!
拿上枪
Grab the guns!
总部肯定出大事了
Shit has to be goin' down at HQ.
我们得赶紧把枪运过去
We gotta get this shit there now.
走
Go!
你有看见希瓦吗
Have you seen Shiva?
我们被袭击后就没见了
Not since we were hit.
我们能穿过...
We can get through them --
举起手
Hands up.
走吧
Let's move...
"国王陛下"
"Your Highness."
忘了你的剑了
Forgot about your blade.
给我
Give it to me.
我得靠它走路
It's how I can walk.
你可以留着拐杖
You can keep the cane.
我需要你帮忙
I'm gonna need your help.
我们有好长的路要走
We got a big trip ahead of us.
-去哪儿  -你猜
- Where? - ?Guess.
救世堂
The Sanctuary?
答对了
That's right.
大门已经关上了
The gates are down.
四周被行尸包围
It's surrounded by the dead.
他们出不来  我们也进不去
They can't get out. We can't get in.
或许你能帮我
Well, maybe you can help me
把机枪送过去
get our big guns over there
帮助挽回局势
to help remedy that situation.
弹药在车里吗
Ammo's in the truck?
救世堂至少还有三箱
There's another three up at Sanctuary and then some.
快点  给我走
Hurry up. Come on!
你走了这么远
You made it this long.
做了那么多破事
After pulling all the crap you did,
现在却要倒下吗
you're gonna lie down now?
我宁愿死
Better the dead be my end
也不愿当一个暴君的无名小卒
than a despot's meaningless foot soldier.
告诉我
Tell me...
尼根知道你叫什么吗
does Negan know your name?
我就是尼根
I'm Negan.
站起来
Get up.
我不会让你利用我伤害我的子民
I will not let you use me to hurt my people.
你的子民
"Your people"?
你是说那些被你哄骗
You mean all those sheep you rooked
以为你是王的奴才吗
into thinking you're a king?
我听说过你的事
Yeah, I heard your story.
我们都听说过
We all did.
我们走  快点
Let's go. Now. Move!
你在马戏团工作吗
You work at a circus?
不在
No.
我曾觉得有可能  但想想不对
Yeah, I thought maybe, but nah.
马戏团可不会善待动物
They don't treat animals too nice at the circus.
而那只猫特别钟爱你
And that cat just loves you.
它给了你一切  不是吗
It gave you everything, didn't it?
给了你手段  让你编故事
Gave you an angle, a story.
不得不佩服你
Got to hand it to you --
你真有一套
you played your cards good.
把子民耍得团团转
You played "Your people" Good.
他们深信你的鬼话
They ate that horseshit right up.
为你种庄稼
They grew food for you.
为你建高墙
Built those walls for you.
见鬼  瞧瞧
Hell, look at that.
你害死了他们  他们依然追随着你
You got them all killed -- they're still following you.
但没了那只老虎
But take away that tiger...
你还算什么
what's left?
不过是某个穿着戏服的骗子
Just some meaningless con man in a costume.
里面还有你的人活着吗
You got people still alive in there?
但愿如此
Let it be so.
我们找辆车坐  然后离开这里
We're getting into something with wheels, and we're getting out of here.
结束了  好吗
It's over, okay?!
你试过了  结束了
You took your shot -- it's over!
妄想狂
Delusions of grandeur.
起来
Come on.
该死
Dammit!
行尸快过来了
The dead are nearly upon us.
把剑给我
Give me my sword.
我们可以一起抵御它们
We can fight 'em together.
你在做什么
The hell are you doing?!
离开这里
Gettin' out of here. ?
我一个人站不稳
I can't stand on my own.
我爬不过去
I can't climb that.
你不用爬过去
You don't need to. ?
就这样吧
Is what it is.
尼根本希望我把你
Negan was hoping to have your ass
拴在救世堂的栅栏上
chained to the Sanctuary fence...
你  寡妇
You, the Widow...
瑞克
Rick.
但把你的首级串在矛上也行
But your head on a pike will do just fine.
也许可以弄乱点
Maybe break it up a little,
不用那么对称
avoid the obvious symmetry.
4号门
我可以告诉你们其他人在哪
I can tell you where the others are.
别杀我
Just let me live!
他们躲起来了
They're hiding out,
等其他救世军出现
waiting for other Saviors to show up.
慢慢出来
Nice and slow.
我没武器
I'm unarmed.
看
Look.
陛下  你的腿
Your Majesty, your leg!
我没事
I'm okay.
杰瑞
Jerry...
我借用一下
I'm going to borrow this for a sec.
杰瑞  我能...
Jerry, I can --
陛下
Your Majesty.
你不需要那样称呼我
You don't need to call me that.
老兄
Dude...
我需要
yes, I do.
你的人
Your people...
他们在哪
...where are they?
你不能告诉他们是我说的
You can't tell them I told you.
你必须答应我  求求你
You have to promise. Please!
你想死吗
Hey, do you wanna die?
我问你的人在哪
I asked you where your people are --
都把枪放下
Lower your guns now!
雅戈  求你了
Yago, please, man.
乔伊自己搞砸了  开火
Joey just pooched it. Light 'em up.
4号门
该死
Shitballs.
待在我身后  陛下
Get behind me, Your Majesty.
不
No.
谢谢你  陛下
Thank you, Your Majesty.
为什么
For what?
因为你是一个超酷的兄弟
For being such a cool dude.
我们需要结束这一切
We need to end this.
关于你朋友  你骗了我们对吗
You were lying to us about your friends, huh?
对  我骗了你们
Yeah. I was.
现在  我们需要结束这一切
Now, we need to end this.
行  走开吧  女士
Okay. Walk away, lady.
你们不能把枪带走
You're not going anywhere with those guns.
不  我们要带走
Nah. We are.
它们要被送去某个地方
They got someplace to be.
我拿到了你们朋友的弹药
I've got your pal's ammo.
打完那些行尸  你们还剩多少子弹
How many bullets you got left after all those walkers?
三颗  四颗
Three? Four?
你何不过来亲眼看看
Why don't you come at us and find out?
我们就在这
We're right here.
宝贝  继续说
Honey, let's keep talking.
我们最不缺的就是时间
We got all the time in the world.
你以前战斗过吗
Have you ever fought before?
你见过我战斗
You've seen me fight.
我是说之前
Before this.
行尸
The dead.
还在树林里遇到过一次强盗
A marauder in the woods once.
-你和他战斗了吗  -是的
- You fought him? - ?Yes.
我先上
Me...
然后希瓦上
then Shiva.
我受过很长时间的训练
I have trained for a very long time.
我也没有中断训练
And I have continued,
从很久之前直到现在
from long before this till now.
我每天都在不断练习
And I have practiced for days on end.
准备好了成为我必须成为的人
I am ready to become what I must.
"成为"吗
"To become"?
对
Yes.
让自己变成必须变成的样子
To will myself into what I must be.
我以前是动物园管理员
I was a zookeeper.
我原来...很温和
I was...meek.
周末的日场  无数个夜晚
Those weekend matinees, those nights.
有一次  工作期间
And then, at work,
一头五百磅重的老虎需要救助
a 500-pound tiger needed my help.
它一直在流血...
And as she bled...
我没有立即跳进它的围场
I did not just leap into her enclosure.
我也没有被深层本能
I was not seized by any...
吓得不知所措
deep-seated instinct.
当时仅仅
They were only...
过了几秒
a few seconds that passed...
但我已在心中盘算过
but I deliberated.
我想过要去救它
I thought about doing it,
权衡了接近这样一头猛兽的风险
weighing the risk of approaching such a beast.
我也想过不去救它
And I thought about not doing it.
我站在原地  不断思索我该成为谁
I stood there, considering who I'd be in either iteration.
最后我决定成为那个跳进去的人
And I decided I wanted to be the one who leapt.
多年后
So, many years later...
本杰明告诉了我  我早已知道
Benjamin was the one who told me what I already knew,
却看不清的事实
but couldn't hear...
"如果需要你当英雄"
"If you're asked to be the hero...
"就去当英雄"
be the hero."
我现在准备好了
I'm now ready.
终于准备好了
Finally.
我想通了
I've deliberated.
已经决定好要成为怎样的人
I've made the decision on who I will be.
你的转变简单吗
Was it easier for you?
你是一直都是这样吗
Or have you always been this way?
这么坚强
This strong?
这么勇敢
This brave?
还是说你决定成为现在的你
Or did you decide to be who you are today?
我决定的
I decided.
和你一样
Just like you.
但命运也会决定一些事
But life ?decided some things, too.
确实决定过
It does.
以后也会决定
It will.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
他们拿走枪了吗
Did they get the guns?
我们无能为力
Nothing we can do about it.
我扶国王
I've got the King.
我们必须通知瑞克
We have to get word to Rick!
如果他们把机枪运到救世堂...
If they ferry those machine guns to the Sanctuary...
他们不会运到救世堂的
They're not getting them to the Sanctuary.
我们拿到枪了
We got the guns.
你看起来真狼狈
You look like shit.
我们去看看那混蛋是否活着
Let's go see if this asshole's alive.
陛下
Your Majesty!
行不通的
This ain't gonna work.
你们必须留下我  我拖后腿了
You gotta leave me. I'm slowing you down.
不  你不能这样
No. You don't get to do that.
快来  我要没子弹了
Come on. I'm almost out of ammo.
强腐蚀性
我过不去
I can't...
别管我了
You can't.
你们快走吧
Y-You two have to just go.
扶他下来
Lower him down to me.
以西结
Ezekiel!
快走  我拖住它们
Just go! I'll hold them off!
以西结  我们能带走你
Ezekiel, we can get you away.
你们不能
You can't!
我不能离开你  陛下
I can't leave you, Your Majesty.
拜托  快走啊
C'mon, man, just go!
你是我的国王
You're my king!
我不是
No, I'm not!
我不是你的国王
I'm not your King!
我不是你的陛下
I'm not "Your Majesty"!
看看眼前的这些东西
Look at what's in front of us!
它们才是真实的
That's what's real!
走
Go.
我不是国王
I ain't no king!
我什么都不是
I ain't nothing.
只是个普通人
I'm just some guy.
碰巧发现了...
Some guy who found...
希瓦而已
Shiva...
快走
C'mon.
希瓦
Shiva!
快跑  姑娘
Run, girl!
不  不
No! No!
放开我  杰瑞
Please, Jerry!
该死的  我要去帮她
Dammit, let me help her!
你帮不了
You can't.
危险物质